Guide to the Edwin and Terry Murray Collection of Role-Playing Games, 1972-2017 RL.00924
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Modules, Manuals, and Campaign Volumes, 1973-2011; 2399 Volumes
  - Al-Qadim, 3
    - Monstrous Compendium: Appendix (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1992 (Volume 813)
    - The Complete Sha'ir's Handbook (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 224)
  - Alternity, 4
    - Beyond Science (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2000 (Volume 1033)
    - Campaign Kit (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 1024)
    - Dataware (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 1032)
    - Gamemaster guide (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 1025)
    - Gamemaster Guide and Player's Handbook: Fast Play Rules (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1998 (Volume 1794)
    - Gamma World: Campaign Setting (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2000 (Volume 1036)
    - Incident at Exile (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1999 (Volume 1030)
    - Mindwalking: a Guide to Psionics (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1999 (Volume 1034)
    - Player's Handbook (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 1037)
    - Starships (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1999 (Volume 1031)
    - Tangents (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1999 (Volume 1035)
  - Amazing Engine, 5
    - Big Hunters (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1993 (Volume M1)
    - Universe Book: for Faerie, Queen, & Country (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1993 (Volume M1)
  - Arduin, 6
    - Caliban (Berkeley, CA: Grimoire Games), 1979 (Volume 1577)
    - Death Heart (Berkeley, CA: Grimoire Games), 1980 (Volume 1574)
    - The Arduin Adventure (Berkeley, CA: Grimoire Games), 1980 (Volume 1682)
    - The Citadel of Thunder (Berkeley, CA: Grimoire Games), 1979 (Volume 1575)
    - The Homling Tower (Berkeley, CA: Grimoire Games), 1979 (Volume 1576)
    - The Last Grimoire (Boulder, CO: Dragon Tree Press), 1984 (Volume 1724)
  - Ars Magica, 7
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream (Stone Mountain, GA: White Wolf), 1992 (Volume 530)
    - A Winter Tale (Stone Mountain, GA: White Wolf), 1991 (Volume 525)
    - Black Death (Stone Mountain, GA: White Wolf), 1991 (Volume 547)
    - Deadly Legacy (Stone Mountain, GA: White Wolf), 1992 (Volume 549)
    - Faeries (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1995 (Volume 559)
    - Festival of the Damned (Northfield, MN: Atlas Games), 1991 (Volume 516)
    - Hedge Magic (Stone Mountain, GA: White Wolf), 1997 (Volume 544)
    - Houses of Hermes (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1994 (Volume 558)
    - Lion of the North (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1994 (Volume 557)
    - Medieval Handbook (Stone Mountain, GA: White Wolf), 1994 (Volume 550)
    - Mistridge (Stone Mountain, GA: White Wolf), 1992 (Volume 552)
    - More Mythic Places (Stone Mountain, GA: White Wolf), undated (Volume 548)
    - Mythic Europe (Stone Mountain, GA: White Wolf), 1992 (Volume 551)
    - Mythic Places (Stone Mountain, GA: White Wolf), undated (Volume 526)
    - Pact of Pasaquine (Stone Mountain, GA: White Wolf), 1991 (Volume 546)
    - Parma Fabula (Stone Mountain, GA: White Wolf), 1997 (Volume 542)
    - Pax Dei (Stone Mountain, GA: White Wolf), undated (Volume 528)
    - Shamans (Stone Mountain, GA: White Wolf), 1993 (Volume 553)
    - Stormrider (Stone Mountain, GA: White Wolf), 1991 (Volume 545)
    - The Art of Magic (Stone Mountain, GA: White Wolf), 1994 (Volume 531)
    - The Art of Magic (Stone Mountain, GA: White Wolf), 1996 (Volume 543)
    - The Maleficium (Stone Mountain, GA: White Wolf), 1992 (Volume 527)
    - The Sorcerer's Slave (Northfield, MN: Atlas Games), 1990 (Volume 518)
    - The Wizard's Grimoire (Stone Mountain, GA: White Wolf), 1993 (Volume 554)
    - Trial by Fire (Northfield, MN: Atlas Games), 1991 (Volume 517)
    - Tribunals of Hermes: Iberia (Stone Mountain, GA: White Wolf), undated (Volume 556)
    - Tribunals of Hermes: Rome (Stone Mountain, GA: White Wolf), 1993 (Volume 555)
    - Twelfth Night (Stone Mountain, GA: White Wolf), 1993 (Volume 529)
  - Battletech, 8
    - Federated Suns (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 2000 (Volume 924)
    - Maximum Tech (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 1997 (Volume 1596)
    - Periphery (Chicago, IL: FASA Corporation), 2000 (Volume 923)
    - The Fires of Hell (WizKids, Inc. (Catalyst Game Labs)), 2009 (Volume M6)
  - Birthright, 10
    - Blood Enemies: Abominations of Cerilia (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 990)
    - King of the Giantdowns (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1997 (Volume 1004)
    - Legends of the Hero-Kings (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 876)
    - Player's Secrets of Ariya (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 885)
    - Player's Secrets of Baruk-Azhik (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 883)
    - Player's Secrets of Binsada (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 882)
    - Player's Secrets of Endier (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 879)
    - Player's Secrets of Halskapa (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 881)
    - Player's Secrets of Hogunmark (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1998 (Volume 1002)
    - Player's Secrets of Ilien (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 888)
    - Player's Secrets of Khourane (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 890)
    - Player's Secrets of Medoere (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 880)
    - Player's Secrets of Roesone (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 878)
    - Player's Secrets of Stjordvik (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 892)
    - Player's Secrets of Talinie (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 887)
    - Player's Secrets of Tuarhievel (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 891)
    - Player's Secrets of Tuornen (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 889)
    - Sword and Crown (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 1000)
    - The Book of Magecraft (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 877)
    - The Book of Priestcraft (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1997 (Volume 1001)
    - The Sword of Roele (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 884)
    - Tribes of the Heartless Waste (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1997 (Volume 1003)
    - Warlock of the Stonecrowns (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 886)
  - Blue Planet, 11
    - Archipelago: A Guide to the Islands (Tucker, GA: Holistic Design Inc.), 1998 (Volume 711)
    - Welcome to Blue Planet (Columbia, MO: Biohazard Games), 1997 (Volume 709)
  - Bubblegum Crisis, 12
    - Before and After (Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games), 1997 (Volume 1390)
    - EX: The Extreme Anime Roleplaying Expanison (Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games), 1998 (Volume 1283)
    - MegaTokyo 2033 (Berkeley, CA: R. Talsorian Games), 1996 (Volume 1389)
  - Buck Rogers: The 25th Century, 13
    - A Matter of Gravitol (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1991 (Volume 988)
    - Buck Rogers in the 25th Century (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 976)
    - Deimos Mandate (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1991 (Volume 972)
    - Earth in the 25th Century (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 973)
    - Hardware (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1992 (Volume 982)
    - Inner Worlds (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1991 (Volume 989)
    - Luna (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1991 (Volume 986)
    - Mars in the 25th Century (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 975)
    - NEO in the 25th Century (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 974)
    - No Humans Allowed (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1992 (Volume 981)
    - Phases of the Moon (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1991 (Volume 985)
    - Sargasso of Space (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1991 (Volume 987)
    - The Belt (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1991 (Volume 984)
  - Cadillacs and Dinosaurs, 14
    - Cadillacs and Dinosaurs (Bloomington, IL: GDW, Inc. ), 1990 (Volume 1110)
  - Call of Cthulhu, 15
    - 1920's Investigators' Companion: Equipment and Resources (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1993 (Volume 150)
    - 1920's Investigators' Companion: Occupations and Skills (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1994 (Volume 138)
    - 1990's Handbook: Modern Background for Call of Cthulhu (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1995 (Volume 20)
    - A Resection of Time: The Strange Case of Kyle Woodson: A Scenario (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1997 (Volume 22)
    - Adventures in Arkham Country: Five Classic Adventures (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1993 (Volume 743)
    - Adventures in Arkham Country: Five Frightening Tales in Lovecraft Country (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1993 (Volume 149)
    - Alone Against The Wendigo: Solitaire Adventure in Canada's Wilds (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1985 (Volume 4)
    - Arkham Unveiled: Adventures and Background in the Home of Miskatonic University (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1990 (Volume 141)
    - At Your Door: A Campaign of Terror and Madness in the Days to Come (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1990 (Volume 18)
    - Before the Fall: Innsmouth Adventures Prior to the Great Raid of 1928 (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1998 (Volume 165)
    - Beyond the Mountains of Madness: An Epic Campaign and Sourcebook (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1999 (Volume 39)
    - Blood Brothers 2: Nine Single-Night Adventures at the Movies (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1992 (Volume 135)
    - Blood Brothers: 13 Tales of Terror (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1990 (Volume 129)
    - Call of Cthulhu Keeper's Kit: Sanity Saving Keeper's Screen, 5th edition (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), undated (Volume 139)
    - Call of Cthulhu Keeper's Screen (no place: Chaosium Inc.), undated (Volume 37)
    - Call of Cthulhu Roleplaying Game (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2002 (Volume 36)
    - Call of Cthulhu: Dire Documents, 5th edition (), undated (Volume 128)
    - Call of Cthulhu: Fantasy Roleplaying in the Worlds of H.P. Lovecraft, 4th edition (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1989 (Volume 113)
    - Call of Cthulhu: Horror Roleplaying in the Worlds of H.P. Lovecraft (includes Investigator Sheets and Dire Documents), 5th edition (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1992 (Volume 126)
    - Call of Cthulhu: Horror Roleplaying in the Worlds of H.P. Lovecraft, 5.5 edition (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1998 (Volume 116)
    - Call of Cthulhu: Horror Roleplaying in the Worlds of H.P. Lovecraft, 5.6 edition (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1999 (Volume 38)
    - Call of Cthulhu: Investigating Sheets, 5th edition (), undated (Volume 127)
    - Call of Cthulhu: Investigator's Book (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1983 (Volume 742)
    - Coming Full Circle (Seattle, WA: Pagan Publishing), 1995 (Volume 125)
    - Cthulhu by Gaslight: Horror Roleplaying in 1890's England (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1988 (Volume 31)
    - Cthulhu Casebook: A Plethora of Plots and Adventures (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1990 (Volume 145)
    - Cthulhu Now: Modern Background and Adventures for Call of Cthulhu Roleplaying (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1987 (Volume 17)
    - Cure of Cthulhu: A Campaign of Desparate Struggle Against the Brotherhood (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1990 (Volume 146)
    - Curse of the Chthonians: Four Odysseys into Deadly Intrigue (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1984 (Volume 1)
    - Dark Designs: Occult Terros in 1890's England (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1991 (Volume 32)
    - Day of the Beast (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1998 (Volume 164)
    - Dead Reckonings (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1998 (Volume 163)
    - Death in Dunwich (Kirkwood, NJ: Theatre of the Mind), 1983 (Volume 9)
    - Delta Green: A Call of Cthulhu Sourcebook of Modern Horror and Conspiracy from Pagan Publishing (Seattle, WA: Pagan Publishing), 1996 (Volume 117)
    - Devil's Children (Columbia, MO: Pagan Publishing), 1992 (Volume 133)
    - Dreamlands: Roleplaying Beyond the Wall of Sleep, 2nd edition (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1988 (Volume 30)
    - Escape from Innsmouth: Daring Adventures in Lovecraft Country (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1992 (Volume 152)
    - Escape from Innsmouth: Second Edition, Expanded and Revised (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1997 (Volume 160)
    - Fatal Experiments: Three Investigations into the Sinister and Macabre (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1990 (Volume 16)
    - Fearful Passages: Nine Terrifying Journeys on Three Continents (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1992 (Volume 151)
    - Glozel Est Authentique (Kirkwood, NJ: Theatre of the Mind), 1984 (Volume 12)
    - Green and Pleasant Land: The British 1920's-30's Cthulhu Sourcepack (Eastwood, Notts, UK: Games Workshop Ltd. ), 1987 (Volume 397)
    - Grimrock Isle: A Chilling Solo Adventure and Campaign Book in One (no place; Chaosium Inc.), 1990 (Volume 399)
    - Horror's Heart: A Short Call of Cthulhu Campaign in Montreal (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1996 (Volume 148)
    - In the Shadows: Three Scenarios for Call of Cthulhu, 1st edition (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1995 (Volume 158)
    - Keeper's Compendium: Blasphemous Knowledge and Forbidden Secrets (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1993 (Volume 155)
    - Keeper's Kit: A Fine Selection of Call of Cthulhul Accessories (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), undated (Volume 25)
    - Keeper's Screen (no place: Chaosium Inc.), undated (Volume 26)
    - King of Chicago and The Secret of Marseilles (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1994 (Volume 156)
    - Kingsport: The City in the Mists (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1991 (Volume 144)
    - Last Rites: Four Present-Day Adventures for Call of Cthulhu (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1999 (Volume 35)
    - Lurking Fears: Six Harrowing Encounters with the Cthulhu Mythos (Lockport, NY: Triad Entertaiments), 1990 (Volume 131)
    - Mansions of Madness (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1990 (Volume 15)
    - Minions: Fifteen Brief Encounters (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1997 (Volume 161)
    - Miskatonic U. Graduate Kit: Artifacts from the World's Scariest University (no place: Chaosium Inc.), undated (Volume 27)
    - Miskatonic University Anarctic Expedition Pack for Beyond the Mountains of Madness (none), undated (Volume 119)
    - Mortal Coils (Seattle, WA: Pagan Publishing), 1998 (Volume 120)
    - No Man's Land: WWI Mythos Actions with the Lost Battalion (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1998 (Volume 34)
    - Of Keys and Gates (Seattle, WA: Tynes Cowan Corporation), 1994 (Volume 136)
    - Pursuit to Kadath (Kirkwood, NJ: Theatre of the Mind), 1983 (Volume 11)
    - Return to Dunwich: Adventure and Background for a Forgotten Village in Lovecraft Country (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1991 (Volume 142)
    - S. Petersen's Field Guide to Creatures of the Dreamlands: An Album of Entities from the Land Beyond the Wall of Sleep (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1989 (Volume 396)
    - S. Petersen's Field Guide to Cthulhu Monsters: A Field Observer's Handbook of Preternatural Entities (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1988 (Volume 395)
    - Sacrements of Evil: Six Adventures of Victorian Horror (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1993 (Volume 33)
    - Secrets: Four One-Session Fright-Night Adventures (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1997 (Volume 24)
    - Shadows of Yog-Sothoth: A Global Campaign to Save Mankind (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1982 (Volume 3)
    - Strange Aeons: Three Unusual Times and Places (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1995 (Volume 114)
    - Taint of Madness: Insanity and Dread within Asylum Walls, 1st edition (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1995 (Volume 124)
    - Tales of the Miskatonic Valley: Uncovering Forbidden Secrets in Lovecraft County (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1991 (Volume 143)
    - Terror Australis (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1987 (Volume 130)
    - Terror from the Stars (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1986 (Volume 6)
    - The 1920's Investigatior's Companion: A Core Game Book for Players (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1997 (Volume 166)
    - The Arkham Evil (Kirkwood, NJ: Theatre of the Mind), 1983 (Volume 8)
    - The Asylum and Other Tales (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1983 (Volume 5)
    - The Bermuda Triangle: Secrets of the Devil's Triangle (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1998 (Volume 23)
    - The Cairo Guidebook: The Lure of the Nile (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1995 (Volume 157)
    - The Compact Arkham Unveiled: A New England Haven for Investigators (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1995 (Volume 159)
    - The Compact Trail of Tsathoggua: Second Edition, Reset and Revised (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1997 (Volume 162)
    - The Complete Dreamlands: Fourth Edition, Expanded and Revised (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1997 (Volume 29)
    - The Complete Masks of Nyarlathotep (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1996 (Volume 154)
    - The Creature Companion: A Core Game Book for Keepers (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1998 (Volume 122)
    - The Dreaming Stone: Against the Crawling Chaos (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1997 (Volume 28)
    - The Fungi from Yuggoth: Desperate Adventures Against the Brotherhood (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1984 (Volume 2)
    - The Golden Dawn: A Sourcebook of Victorian Occult Intrigue for Call of Cthulhu from Pagan Publishing (Seattle, WA: Pagan Publishing), 1996 (Volume 118)
    - The Great Old Ones: Six Terrifying Adventures Against Awesome Mythos Menaces (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1989 (Volume 147)
    - The Horrible Secret of Monhegan Island (no place: Grenadier Models Inc.), 1984 (Volume 10)
    - The London Guidebook: 1920's Roleplaying in the Capital of the World (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1996 (Volume 153)
    - The New Orleans Guidebook (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1997 (Volume 167)
    - The Realm of Shadows (Seattle, WA: Pagan Publishing), 1997 (Volume 121)
    - The Stars Are Right!: Seven Modern Horrors (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1992 (Volume 19)
    - The Statue of the Sorcerer and The Vanishing Conjurer (Eastwood, Notts, UK: Games Workshop Ltd. ), 1986 (Volume 394)
    - The Thing at the Threshold: an Adventure into Darkness (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1992 (Volume 134)
    - The University Guide Book: Miskatonic University (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1995 (Volume 123)
    - Trail of the Loathsome Slime (Eastwood, Notts, UK: Games Workshop Ltd. ), 1985 (Volume 14)
    - Trail of Tsathogghua (Albany, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1984 (Volume 7)
    - Utatti Asfet: The Eye of Wicked Sight (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1996 (Volume 21)
    - Walker in the Wastes (Seattle, WA: Pagan Publishing), 1994 (Volume 115)
    - Whispers from the Abyss and Other Tales (Kirkwood, NJ: Theatre of the Mind), 1984 (Volume 13)
    - Whispers in the Dark: Four Harrowing Glimpses into the Cthulhu Mythos (Lockport, NY: Triad Entertaiments), 1993 (Volume 132)
    - Ye Booke of Monstres II: More Nightmares for Call of Cthulhu (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1995 (Volume 137)
    - Ye Booke of Monstres: The Aniolowski Collection, Volume 1 (Oakland, CA: Chaosium Inc.), 1994 (Volume 140)
  - Campaign Hexagon, 16
    - Castles, Book 1 (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1978 (Volume 1768)
    - Caves and Caverns (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1982 (Volume 1774)
    - Island, Book 1 (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1978 (Volume 1766)
    - Village, Book 1 (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1978 (Volume 1769)
    - Village, Book 2 (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1978 (Volume 1770)
  - Car Wars, 17
    - Car Wars (Austin, TX: Steve Jackson Games), 1981 (Volume 688)
    - Car Wars: Reference Screen (Austin, TX: Steve Jackson Games), 1981 (Volume 1081)
  - Car Wars & Champions, 18
    - Autoduel Champions (Austin, TX: Steve Jackson Games), 1983 (Volume 2141)
  - Castle Falkenstein, 19
    - Castle Falkenstein: High Adventure in the Steam Age (Chicago, IL: A to Z Printing), 1994 (Volume 246)
    - Comme Il Faut: All Things Right and Proper (Berkely, CA: R. Talsorian Games), 1995 (Volume 245)
    - Six Guns and Sorcery (Berkely, CA: R. Talsorian Games), 1996 (Volume 244)
    - Steamage: Amazing Wonders Through the Power of Steam (Berkely, CA: R. Talsorian Games), 1994 (Volume 243)
    - The Book of Sigils (no place: R. Talsorian Games), 1995 (Volume 248)
    - The Lost Notebook of Leonardo da Vinci: Principia de Mancipium Potentia Magica Universalis (no place: R. Talsorian Games), 1995 (Volume 247)
    - The Memoirs of Auberon of Faerie (no place: R. Talsorian Games), 1997 (Volume 249)
  - Central Casting, 20
    - Heroes for Tomorrow (Van Nuys, CA: Task Force Games), 1989 (Volume 1649)
    - Heroes Now! (Van Nuys, CA: Task Force Games), 1991 (Volume 1648)
    - Heroes of Legend (Van Nuys, CA: Task Force Games), 1988 (Volume 1650)
  - Champions, 21
    - Aaron Allston's Strike Force: Champions Campaign Sourcebook (#42) (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1988 (Volume 2105)
    - Alien Enemies (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1990 (Volume 2271)
    - Allies (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1993 (Volume 2256)
    - Atlantis (#441) (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1995 (Volume 2162)
    - Atlas Unleashed (#48) (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises) (Volume 2101)
    - Blood Fury (Roseville, MN: Atlas Games), 1996 (Volume 2157)
    - C.L.O.W.N.: Criminal Legion of Wacky Non-conformists (#46) (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1989 (Volume 2103)
    - Challenges for Champions (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1989 (Volume 2280)
    - Champions III (San Mateo, CA: Hero Games), 1984 (Volume 2114)
    - Champions in 3-D (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1990 (Volume 2273)
    - Champions of the North (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1992 (Volume 2261)
    - Champions Presents (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1991 (Volume 2267)
    - Champions Presents #2 (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1993 (Volume 2259)
    - Champions Universe (#421) (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1992 (Volume 2150)
    - Champions: The Super Role-playing Game and HERO System Rules (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1989 (Volume 2253)
    - Champions: The Super Role-Playing Game! (San Mateo, CA: Hero Games), 1985 (Volume 2139)
    - Classic Enemies (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1989 (Volume 2281)
    - Classic Organizations (#416) (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1991 (Volume 2172)
    - Danger International (San Mateo, CA: Hero Games), 1985 (Volume 2112)
    - Dark Champions: Heroes of Vengeance (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1993 (Volume 2252)
    - Day of the Destroyer (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1990 (Volume 2276)
    - Deathstroke (San Mateo, CA: Hero Games), 1983 (Volume 2118)
    - Demons Rule (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1990 (Volume 2272)
    - Enemies (San Mateo, CA: Hero Games), 1981 (Volume 2137)
    - Enemies Assemble! (#440) (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1995 (Volume 2163)
    - Enemies for Hire (#439) (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1995 (Volume 2164)
    - Enemies II (San Mateo, CA: Hero Games), 1982 (Volume 2134)
    - Enemies: The International File (#30) (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1988 (Volume 2126)
    - Enemies: Villainy Unbound (#36) (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1988 (Volume 2122)
    - Escape from Stronghold (#2) (San Mateo, CA: Hero Games), 1981 (Volume 2136)
    - European Enemies (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1991 (Volume 2268)
    - Foxbat Unhinged (Roseville, MN: Atlas Games), 1996 (Volume 2158)
    - Gadgets! (#23) (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1986 (Volume 2133)
    - Gamemaster's Screen for Champions, 2nd Edition (San Mateo, CA: Hero Games), 1981 (Volume 2135)
    - GM Screen and Accessories for Champions (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises) (Volume 2283)
    - Golden Age Champions (#436) (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1994 (Volume 2167)
    - Heroic Adventures, Volume 1 (Elk Grove, CA: Gold Rush Games), 1996 (Volume 2156)
    - High Tech Enemies (Charlottesville, VA: Iron Crown Enterprises), 1992 (Volume 2260)